legalservicesindia.com 2019-03-21

# Objective of legal service India

**Our Commitment To Privacy  
**Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

This notice applies to all information collected from or submitted to the following Legal Service India.com Web site(s), but to make this notice easier to read we will refer here only "our Web site", meaning either Legal Service India.com and legalservicesindia.com

Our Web site contains links to other Web sites operated by third parties. Legal Service India.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or policies of such third party Web sites.

**The Information We Collect**  
Our Web site is not set up to automatically collect personally-identifiable information from each visitors to our Web site. It does recognize the home server of visitors, but not e-mail addresses. For example, we can tell which Internet Service Provider our visitors use, but not the names, addresses or other information about our visitors that would allow us to identify the particular visitors to our Web site. This information is used only for internal purposes by our technical support staff.

Our Web site does track certain information about the visits to our Web site. For example, we compile statistics that show the numbers and frequency of visitors to our Web site and its individual pages. These aggregated statistics are used internally to improve our Web site and for product development and marketing purposes generally. Those aggregated statistics may also be provided to advertisers and other third parties, but again, the statistics contain no personal information and cannot be used to gather such information.

In a few areas on our Web site, we may ask you to provide information that will enable us to verify whether you are entitled to access and use certain information, materials and services available from our Web site, or to enable us to enhance your site visit, to assist you with customer service or technical support issues, or to follow up with you after your visit, or to otherwise support your customer relationship with Legal Service India.com. It is completely optional for you to participate. However, failure to participate may mean that you cannot access and use certain information, materials and services.

For example, we may request information from you when you:  
(a) Log-on to certain areas of our Web site, where you may be prompted to provide us with your user name and password as a condition to gaining access to certain information, materials or services  
(b) Register or sign-up to subscribe to a service Subscribe to a newsletter or desire to be added to our mailing lists for other products or services  
(c) Place an order  
(d) Participate in a sweepstakes or other promotional offer  
(e) Provide feedback in an online survey.

In each of the instances above, we typically ask for your name, e-mail address, phone number, address, the type of business you are in, product preference information, any applicable identification number or password that we may require, as well as other similar personal information that is needed to register or subscribe you to services or offers. On occasion, we may ask for additional information to enable us to provide you with access to and use of certain information, materials and services. In the case of mailed materials, you will be able to "unsubscribe" to these mailings at any time.

**How We Use Information**  
Legal Service India.com only uses your personal information for specific purposes

The personal information you provide to us when using our Web site -- such as your name, postal or e-mail address or telephone number -- will be kept confidential and used to support your customer relationship with Legal Service India.com. It also may be used to notify you of special offers, updated information and new products and services from Legal Service India.com, or offers from third parties that we think may be of interest to you. Agents or contractors of Legal Service India.com who are given access to your personal information will be required to keep the information confidential and not use it for any other purpose than to carry out the services they are performing for Legal Service India.com.

Legal Service India.com may enhance or merge your information collected at its site with data from third parties for purposes of marketing products or services to you.

The ads appearing on this Web site are delivered to you by _leadhound, commission junction, linkshare_ and _reporting.net_ our Web advertising partners. Information about your visit to this site, such as number of times you have viewed an ad (but not your name, address or other personal information), is used to serve ads to you on this site. In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser.

Circumstances may arise where we are required to disclose your personal information to third parties for purposes other than to support your customer relationship with Legal Service India.com, such as in connection with a corporate divestiture or dissolution where we sell all or a portion of our business or assets (including our associated customer lists containing your personal information), or if disclosure is required by law or is pertinent to judicial or governmental investigations or proceedings.

Y **ou can opt-out of receiving further marketing from Legal Service India.com at any time**  
We will send you information about our various products and services, or other products and services we feel may be of interest to you. Only Legal Service India.com (or agents or contractors working on behalf of Legal Service India.com and under confidentiality agreements) will send you these direct mailings. If you do not want to receive such mailings, simply tell us when you give us your personal information. Or, at any time you can easily opt-out of receiving further marketing from Legal Service India.com by clicking here.

**Our Commitment To Data Security**  
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

**How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information**  
You can request a copy of the personally-identifiable information that Legal Service India.com has collected about you via the Internet by contacting our Information Privacy Manager at the address below. You can also have factual inaccuracies in this information corrected by contacting this same person.

**How To Contact Us**  
If you would like to contact us for any reason regarding our privacy practices, kindly e-mail us at the following addresses:  
**E-Mailing address** : [admin@legalserviceindia.com](mailto:admin@legalserviceindia.com)

Print This Article 

## How To Submit Your Article:

### Follow the Procedure Below To Submit Your Articles

Submit your Article by using our online form **Click here**  
Note* we only accept **Original Articles** , we will not accept Articles Already Published in other websites.  
For Further Details Contact: [ editor@legalserviceindia.com](mailto:editor@legalserviceindia.com)

## [ Divorce by Mutual Consent in Delhi/NCR](http://www.legalserviceindia.com/helpline/mutual_consent_divorce.htm)

Right Away Call us at Ph no: 9650499965
